Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
: Ahh...
: 啊...
Nothing quite like
a relaxing stroll
没有什么很像
轻松漫步
deep  in Jellyfish Fields.
水母田深处。
I'd know that sound anywhere.
我在任何地方都知道这个声音。
It's a terrifying shriek.
这是令人恐惧的尖叫声。
But where's it coming from?
但它从哪里来？
Patrick, what is with
all this shrieking?
帕特里克，怎么了
所有这些尖叫声？
You know I walk
here on Tuesdays?
你知道我走路
周二在这里吗？
Sorry, SpongeBob,
that wasn't me.
对不起，海绵宝宝，
那不是我。
Patrick, I know I heard
a terrifying shriek.
帕特里克，我知道我听到了
一声可怕的尖叫声。
So did I, SpongeBob
我也是，海绵宝宝
but I was
just mimicking it.
但我当时
So you were
mimicking it.
所以你是
模仿它。
Patrick, please don't
do that, it is really...
帕特里克，请不要
这样做，真的是……
Wait a minute.
等一下。
If the shriek wasn't
coming from you
如果尖叫声不是
来自你
then were was it...
那么是不是...
It's over there behind
that kelp shrub.
就在后面那儿
那个海带灌木。
The terrifying shriek must
have come from this clam.
恐怖的尖叫声一定是
来自这个蛤。
Hey, Patrick, I think there's
something wrong with...
嘿，帕特里克，我想有
有什么问题...
Oh, what are
we gonna do?
哦，什么是
我们要做什么？
Well, the last time
I remembered coughing like that
嗯，最后一次
我记得我是这样咳嗽的
I was sitting at home eating
a box of kelp jerky.
我坐在家里吃饭
一盒海带干
Oh, and you were coughing
because you got some
stuck in your throat?
哦，你还在咳嗽
因为你有一些
卡在喉咙里了？
I got the TV remote
stuck in my throat.
我拿到了电视遥控器
卡在我的喉咙里。
Patrick,
this clam is choking.
帕特里克，
这蛤蜊窒息了。
Luckily, I come prepared.
幸运的是，我是有准备的。
There, there, clammy.
那里，那里，湿漉漉的。
SpongeBob,
what are you doing?
海绵宝宝，
你在做什么？
They like this.
他们喜欢这样。
You always give
a choking victim
你总是给予
窒息的受害者
the "slimelich"
maneuver first.
“史莱姆利奇”
首先进行机动。
And if that doesn't work
如果这不起作用
you walk away and pretend
like you never saw them before.
你走开并假装
就像你以前从未见过他们一样。
Like this.
像这样。
Ready clam?
准备好蛤蜊了吗？
Patrick: Ohh!
帕特里克：哦！
Well, SpongeBob, I think
I might go catch a movie.
好吧，海绵宝宝，我想
我可能会去看电影。
Hey, what about the clam?
嘿，蛤蜊呢？
What clam? I've never seen
that clam before in my life.
什么蛤？我从未见过
我生命中以前的那个蛤蜊。
But...
但...
Patrick.
帕特里克.
The clam had a baby.
蛤蜊生下了孩子。
That's not a baby,
SpongeBob.
那不是一个婴儿，
海绵宝宝。
Well then,
what could it be?
那么，
可能是什么？
I'll give you a hint.
我给你一个提示。
What's white and round
and comes out of clams?
什么东西又白又圆
是从蛤蜊里出来的？
Their... Eyes?
他们的……眼睛？
No, silly, a volleyball.
不，傻瓜，排球。
A baby volleyball.
婴儿排球。
I got it!
我得到了它！
: Oh.
： 哦。
Good idea,
coming here, Patrick.
好主意，
来这里，帕特里克。
That's my specialty.
这是我的专长。
Having good ideas?
有好主意吗？
Being called Patrick.
被称为帕特里克。
Maybe we should do
some stretches first.
也许我们应该做
首先进行一些伸展运动。
Good idea.
好主意。
Well, that's
my specialty.
嗯，那就是
我的专长。
Having good ideas?
有好主意吗？
Nope, doing some
stretches first.
不，做一些
首先伸展。
Yeah, no, I don't know.
是的，不，我不知道。
The thing's 100 years old, how
should I know?
这东西已经有100年历史了，怎么办？
我应该知道吗？
Yeah, all right, look,
if you don't want it...
是的，好吧，看，
如果你不想要它...
Uh-huh, yeah.
嗯嗯，是的。
...Well, I...
……嗯，我……
Uh, yeah, I'm...
I'm still here.
呃，是的，我是...
我还在这里。
SpongeBob: 138, 139...
海绵宝宝：138、139...
Gentlemen.
先生们。
Hello.
你好。
I couldn't help noticing
我忍不住注意到
what a lovely ball that is.
那是一个多么可爱的球啊。
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Yes.
是的。
I'd sure like to
get a closer look.
我当然愿意
仔细看看。
Oh, we don't mind,
do we, Patrick?
哦，我们不介意，
我们是吗，帕特里克？
Well, just don't
take too long.
好吧，只是不要
花太长时间。
We were just about
to start playing with it.
我们刚刚
开始玩它。
Oh...
哦...
It, uh, won't take
long at all... Ooh.
它，呃，不会需要
一点都长……哦。
It's heavier
than I imagined
比较重
比我想象的
and, uh, shinier too.
而且，呃，也更闪亮。
Where'd you find it?
你在哪里找到的？
We found it  deep
in Jellyfish Fields.
我们发现它很深
在水母田里。
Really?
真的吗？
What was it
doing there?
那是什么
在那里做什么？
Choking a clam.
噎死一只蛤蜊。
Well, um...
嗯，嗯...
what would you say
if I were to offer you
你会说什么
如果我要给你
a small fortune in exchange
for your shiny ball?
一笔小钱作为交换
为了你闪亮的球？
What do you mean,
small fortune?
你是什么意思，
小财？
Whoa, how many more trucks do
you think there'll be, Patrick?
哇，还有多少卡车
你认为会有吗，帕特里克？
Huh?
啊？
Oh, I don't know.
哦，我不知道。
I am getting
kind of hungry, though.
我正在得到
不过有点饿了。
I'll catch up with
you later, SpongeBob.
我会赶上
稍后你，海绵宝宝。
Well, that looks
like the last of 'em.
嗯，看起来
就像他们中的最后一个一样。
The last
of what?
最后一个
什么？
So did you figure out
what you're gonna do
那么你有没有发现
你要做什么
with this fat
stack of cabbage yet?
有了这个脂肪
一堆白菜了吗？
Yup, I mean, nope.
是的，我的意思是，不。
Well, my dad always told me:
嗯，我爸爸总是告诉我：
"When you have money, you need
to do more than just spend it.
“当你有钱的时候，你需要
不仅仅是花钱。
You need to have a plan."
你需要有一个计划。”
Wow, your dad
really told you that?
哇，你爸爸
真的告诉过你了吗？
Well, what he said was
嗯，他说的是
"How many times do I have to
tell you not to stand there?"
“我要经历多少次
叫你不要站在那里？”
But I knew what he meant.
但我知道他的意思。
Hey, Patrick, I know
a good place to go
嘿，帕特里克，我知道
一个好去处
when you don't know
what to buy.
当你不知道的时候
买什么。
The mall.
商场。
Whoo!
呼！
Touchdown!
接地！
Aww...
哇...
Patrick, where'd you go?
帕特里克，你去哪儿了？
Oh, there you are.
哦，你来了。
Patrick, that was
the best shopping day ever.
帕特里克，那是
有史以来最好的购物日。
You can say
that again.
你可以说
再说一遍。
Best shopping day ever.
有史以来最好的购物日。
Patrick, I've got an idea.
帕特里克，我有一个主意。
Really?
真的吗？
Let's go
shopping again
我们走吧
再次购物
and this time...
buy stuff.
而这一次...
买东西。
Oh, wasn't that
incredible, Patrick?
哦，那不是吗
难以置信，帕特里克？
I mean,
with all this money
我的意思是，
用这么多钱
we could've bought
anything in the whole world.
我们本来可以买
全世界的任何事物。
Yup.
是的。
So tell me,
what'd you buy?
所以告诉我，
你买了什么？
A lifetime supply
of strawberry gum.
终身供应
草莓口香糖。
:
Hey, me too.
：
嘿，我也是。
And to think we barely even
put a dent in my fortune.
想想我们甚至几乎
使我的财富受到损害。
French Man:
The following Thursday...
法国人：
接下来的星期四...
Two please.
请两个。
One for me and one for
my best friend, Patrick.
一份给我，一份给
我最好的朋友帕特里克。
I didn't really ask
who they're for?
我真的没有问
他们是为了谁？
Thanks.
谢谢。
There you go.
就这样吧。
It was only 59 cents
for the ice cream.
仅需 59 美分
为了冰淇淋。
Oh, that's OK.
哦，没关系。
I kind of have
more money
我有点有
更多的钱
than I know what
to do with right now.
我不知道是什么
现在就做。
Looks like my ex-wife was wrong.
看来我的前妻错了。
I  am  in the right
line of work.
我是对的
工作线。
Uh, triple "goo-berry"
sundae, please?
呃，三个“goo-berry”
圣代，请吗？
Extra nuts.
额外的坚果。
That's gonna be $2.98.
那将是 2.98 美元。
Uh, hey, Bert, you got like,
eight cents I can borrow?
呃，嘿，伯特，你就像，
八分钱我可以借吗？
Yeah, let me check.
是的，让我检查一下。
No, I don't, Bill, sorry.
不，我不知道，比尔，抱歉。
You know, why is it
I always have money
你知道，为什么会这样
我总是有钱
when  you  need to borrow it?
什么时候需要借？
Well, I don't know
what to say, I...
嗯，我不知道
怎么说呢，我...
Are you gentlemen
low on funds?
你们是先生们吗
资金不足？
Let me help.
让我帮忙。
Here you go.
干得好。
Whoa, uh, that's OK.
哇哦，没关系。
I just need eight cents.
我只需要八美分。
That's OK, I already
got my ice cream, see?
没关系，我已经
我的冰淇淋拿到了，看到了吗？
OK, um... Thanks.
好的，嗯...谢谢。
Sure thing.
当然可以。
Do you need
some too, Bert?
你需要吗
还有一些，伯特？
Excuse me,
can I have some too?
对不起，
我也可以吃一些吗？
Oh, you wanna buy
some ice cream?
哦，你想买吗
一些冰淇淋？
No, I'm allergic
不，我过敏
but... I'll be
your best friend.
但是...我会的
你最好的朋友。
It's a deal.
这是一笔交易。
Hey, I think I could hang out
with this guy for awhile.
嘿，我想我可以出去玩
和这个家伙相处了一段时间。
Me too.
我也是。
Me three.
我三个。
Ice cream?
冰淇淋？
: Yes?
： 是的？
Uh, I'm here
to see SpongeBob.
呃，我在这儿
去看海绵宝宝。
And are you on
the guest list, sir?
你在吗
客人名单，先生？
Well... I don't think so.
嗯...我不这么认为。
Normally, I...
正常情况下，我...
Well, then I'm afraid
I can't let you in, sir.
好吧，那我恐怕
我不能让你进来，先生。
Good day, sir.
美好的一天，先生。
Good day.
再会。
Uh, your shoe's untied.
呃，你的鞋带解开了。
Oh, why so it is.
哦，为什么会这样呢。
Thank you, sir.
谢谢您，先生。
And so he was like,
"Do you wanna buy
some ice cream?"
所以他就像，
“你想买吗
来点冰淇淋吗？”
: Ice cream,
can you imagine?
：冰淇淋，
你能想象吗？
: Yeah.
： 是的。
Ah, I love that story.
啊，我喜欢那个故事。
Uh, hey, guys.
呃，嘿，伙计们。
Have you seen
SpongeBob around?
你见过吗
海绵宝宝在身边吗？
Uh, is that guy
talking to us?
呃，是那个人吗
和我们说话？
Just don't move,
or breathe.
只要别动，
或呼吸。
He might go away.
他可能会离开。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Hey, pal,
watch it.
嘿，朋友，
看着它。
I could buy
and  sell you.
我可以买
并卖掉你。
And I said, "Go ahead,
let's do it right now.
我说：“来吧，
我们现在就做吧。
I got too much hair anyways."
反正我的头发太多了。”
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
That's my name,
don't wear it out.
这是我的名字，
别把它磨损了。
SpongeBob, I gotta
tell you something
I think you should know.
海绵宝宝，我必须
告诉你一些事
我想你应该知道。
Your house is
full of strangers.
你的房子是
充满了陌生人。
Oh, Patrick,
theses aren't strangers.
哦，帕特里克，
这些人并不陌生。
These are 497 of
my closest friends.
这些是 497 个
我最亲密的朋友。
Right, everybody?
对吧，大家？
All: Yeah!
全体：是啊！
That's right!
这是正确的！
All:  : Yeah!
全体： ： 是啊！
Patrick, do you hear that?
帕特里克，你听到了吗？
That is the sound of love.
那是爱的声音。
SpongeBob, if you
keep throwing your
money away like that
海绵宝宝，如果你
继续扔你的
钱就这样消失了
you won't have
any left and then...
你不会有
剩下的，然后...
Excuse me, sir.
对不起，先生。
Is this man
giving you trouble?
这是男人吗
给你添麻烦了？
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Like I was
saying...
就像我以前一样
说……
We don't want
any trouble.
我们不想要
有任何麻烦。
Now just keep moving.
现在继续前进。
Dude, how did
you get in there?
老哥，怎么做到的
你进去了吗？
And I told him, "It's not
that I mind the macaroni.
我告诉他：“这不是
我介意通心粉。
What I mind is..."
我介意的是……”
Sorry about
that, SpongeBob.
抱歉
那个，海绵宝宝。
Won't happen again.
不会再发生了。
No matter,
he's simply jealous
没关系，
他只是嫉妒
of my glamorous new lifestyle.
我迷人的新生活方式。
:
Say, that reminds me.
：
说吧，这让我想起了。
Can I have
some money?
我可以有
一些钱？
Why certainly.
为什么当然。
I always remember to...
我一直记得要...
I forgot, I keep it
in this other pocket.
我忘记了，我保留着
在另一个口袋里。
All:  : Oh?
全部： ：哦？
Uh, will you please
excuse me for a moment?
呃，请你
打扰一下？
Ahh...
啊...
: Ahh!
：啊！
Well, everyone?
嗯，大家呢？
I hope this doesn't put
a damper on things but
我希望这不会
事物的阻尼器但是
I just checked, and well
我刚刚查了一下，还好
it's just that
all my money is...
就是这样
我所有的钱都是...
...gone.
……走了。
Don't be late
for work tomorrow, boy.
不要迟到
明天上班，孩子。
Hey, Patrick.
嘿，帕特里克。
: Oh,
hey, SpongeBob.
：哦，
嘿，海绵宝宝。
What ya doing?
你在做什么？
Oh, the same thing
us sea stars are
usually doing, I guess.
哦，同样的事情
我们海星是
我猜通常会这样做。
Laying up against a rock.
靠着一块岩石躺着。
Patrick,
I was wrong.
帕特里克，
我错了。
The money...
钱...
And about those people
being my friends.
而关于那些人
成为我的朋友。
There is no
right or wrong
没有
对或错
when it comes to
that stuff, SpongeBob.
当谈到
那个东西，海绵宝宝。
There just either is
or there isn't.
只有一个是
或者没有。
Patrick, if having a bunch
of money makes me forget
that you're my best friend
帕特里克，如果有一堆
金钱让我忘记
你是我最好的朋友
then I don't want
any more money, ever again.
那我不想
再来点钱吧。
Well, why didn't
you say so, buddy?
嗯，为什么没有
你说是吗，伙计？
I've been waiting
for someone to go break in
my new volleyball with.
我一直在等待
让某人闯入
我的新排球。
You got another
new volleyball?
你还有另一个
新排球？
Yup, I found it.
是的，我找到了。
Found it, where?
找到了，在哪里？
Inside the Bikini
Bottom diamond mine.
比基尼里面
底部钻石矿。
:
♪ Figaro ♪
：
♪ 费加罗 ♪
♪ Figaro ♪
♪ Figaro-figaro-figaro-figaro-
figaro-figaro-figaro-figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗-费加罗-费加罗-费加罗-
费加罗费加罗费加罗费加罗♪
♪ Fi-ga-ro! ♪
♪ 菲加罗！ ♪
Don't feel bad.
别难过。
He didn't use me
yesterday, either.
他没有利用我
昨天，或者。
♪ La, la-la, la-la,
la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦，啦啦，啦啦，
啦啦啦啦啦♪
I am anxious to look good and
make a strong first impression
我渴望看起来漂亮并且
留下深刻的第一印象
as I share my singing skills
当我分享我的歌唱技巧时
with the famed Bikini Bottom
men's chorus.
著名的比基尼泳裤
男子合唱团。
♪ Ah-la, la-la-la ♪
♪ 啊啦，啦啦啦 ♪
But I needn't be too anxious.
但我不必太着急。
For once they hear
this master's voice
这一次他们听到
这位大师的声音
they'll give me
the lead solo for sure.
他们会给我
肯定是主唱。
♪ Figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗 ♪
Huh?
啊？
Well, looks like
a forlorn SpongeBob
嗯，看起来像
孤独的海绵宝宝
lying sprawled
across the dirt.
趴着
穿过泥土。
Obviously depressed.
明显郁闷了。
Oh, what a lovely day...
噢，多么美好的一天啊……
...for me  .
...为我  。
Huh?
啊？
Squidward,
my playmate, Patrick
章鱼哥，
我的玩伴帕特里克
is away at
a family reunion.
不在
家庭团聚。
Sad and alone.
悲伤而孤独。
I am desperate for
something to do
我很绝望
有事可做
and someone to play with.
和一个可以一起玩的人。
Well, I've got no time
for the likes of you.
好吧，我没有时间
对于像你这样的人。
Squidward, where you going
all dressed up?
章鱼哥，你要去哪里
都盛装打扮了吗？
None of your business?
关你屁事？
Can I come?
我可以来吗？
And... No, you can't.
而且...不，你不能。
Are you going
to a fancy store?
你去吗
去一家高档商店？
A fancy "par-tay?"
一个奇特的“par-tay”？
A hot fancy pants date?
热裤约会？
Can I come?
我可以来吗？
Can I come, can I come...
我可以来吗，我可以来吗……
Can I come, can I come,
can I come?
我可以来吗我可以来吗
我可以来吗？
No, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，
不，不，不。
Does that answer
your questions?
这有答案吗
你的问题？
All except for
that last one.
除
最后一个。
No you can't!
不，你不能！
If you must know
如果你一定要知道
I am going to be
a featured soloist
我将会成为
一位特色独奏家
for an impending
concert performance
对于即将到来的
音乐会表演
with the famed
Bikini Bottom men's choir.
与著名的
比基尼泳裤男子合唱团。
I'm hitting the big time...
我正赶上大事...
Not play time.
不是玩耍时间。
Now if you'll excuse me.
现在请原谅我。
Wow...
哇...
I may not be as good as you
and your buddies, Squidward
我可能不如你
和你的伙伴们，章鱼哥
but I too have a song in my
heart that I wanna share.
但我也有一首歌
我想分享的心。
Ahem... Ahem.
咳咳……咳咳。
Ahem! Ahem!
咳咳！咳咳！
♪ Ahh... ♪
♪ 啊...♪
Au revoir,  SpongeBob.
再见，海绵宝宝。
See you in the nosebleed seats.
在流鼻血的座位上见。
: Ha, ha, ha, ha.
: 哈哈哈哈。
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
SpongeBob:  :
♪ La-la-la-la-la... ♪
海绵宝宝：：
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦……♪
♪ La-la-la-
la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦-
啦啦啦啦♪
Huh?
啊？
♪ Yodel-lay-ee-whoo ♪
♪ 约德尔-莱-伊-呼 ♪
I'm good enough to join
我足够优秀，可以加入
the Bikini Bottom
men's chorus, I promise.
比基尼泳裤
男子合唱团，我保证。
Yuck.
恶心。
Perhaps Squidward didn't see me.
也许章鱼哥没有看到我。
♪ Figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗 ♪
This giant pothole ought
to get his attention.
这个巨大的坑应该
来引起他的注意。
♪ Figaro! ♪
♪ 费加罗！ ♪
...Ohh...
...哦...
Jellyfish: Oh.
海蜇：哦。
♪ ...Oh ♪
♪ ...噢 ♪
Ah, I think I hit
the wrong note back there.
啊，我想我击中了
后面的注释有误。
What the...
什么...
What a lucky break.
多么幸运的一​​次休息。
Now I have
a captive audience.
现在我有
被俘虏的观众。
Squidward: Ahh!
章鱼哥：啊啊！
♪ La... ♪
♪ 啦... ♪
Squidward: Ahh!
章鱼哥：啊啊！
♪ Me-me-me-me ♪
♪ 我我我我 ♪
♪ Me-me-me ♪
♪ 我我我 ♪
Ahh!
啊！
Um, Squidward, could you
keep it down please?
嗯，章鱼哥，你可以吗？
请把它放下来好吗？
I'm trying to find
my starting pitch here.
我正在努力寻找
我的首发位置在这里。
Hey...
嘿...
If that rank amateur,
SpongeBob, embarrasses me
如果那是业余的话，
海绵宝宝让我尴尬了
in front of
the Bikini Bottom choir men
在前面
比基尼泳裤合唱团男子
my life is ruined.
我的生活被毁了。
Oh, I'm almost late
for choir practice.
哦，我快迟到了
用于合唱团练习。
I'd better not run into
SpongeBob again or I'm doomed.
我最好别碰上
海绵宝宝再来一次，否则我就完蛋了。
: Ah-ha-ha-ha.
: 啊哈哈哈哈。
♪ Figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗 ♪
♪ Figaro-figaro-figaro... ♪
♪ 费加罗-费加罗-费加罗... ♪
Stop!
停止！
Stop, stop, stop.
停下来，停下来，停下来。
Ahh!
啊！
I hereby issue you this ticket
for reckless frowning.
我特此向您发出这张票
因为鲁莽的皱眉。
And failing to
listen to my song.
并且未能
听我的歌。
Your song?
你的歌？
What are you,
some kind of...
你是什么，
某种...
That's right,
I'm a singing traffic cop.
没错，
我是一名唱歌的交通警察。
A singing traffic...
歌声中的交通……
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Solo mio ♪
♪ 独奏我 ♪
SpongeBob, I will
be late to practice
海绵宝宝我会的
练习迟到
with all of your
tomfoolery slowing me down.
与你的一切
愚蠢的行为让我放慢了速度。
Yech.
耶赫。
It is a high honor
这是一项崇高的荣誉
to be chosen for
the Bikini Bottom men's chorus
被选为
比基尼泳裤男子合唱团
and you are not going to keep me
from performing my grand solo.
你不会留住我
从表演我的盛大独奏。
♪ Figaro,
figaro-figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗,
费加罗费加罗♪
♪ Figaro, figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗，费加罗 ♪
♪ Fi-ga... ♪
♪ 菲加... ♪
♪ Ro... ♪
♪ 罗... ♪
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
Jellyfish: Oh?
水母：哦？
SpongeBob: ♪ Ohh... ♪
海绵宝宝：♪哦...♪
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
Men's Chorus:
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
男子合唱：
♪ 哦哦哦哦哦哦 ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ 噢-噢-噢-噢-噢-噢-噢-噢 ♪
Just in time.
恰逢其时。
Gentlemen.
先生们。
♪ Ahh... ♪
♪ 啊...♪
Ha, hm...
哈、嗯……
Hm, hm, uh, ha!
嗯嗯嗯嗯哈！
Hm-hum-hum-hum.
嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Chorus: ♪ Ahh... ♪
合唱：♪ 啊...♪
: ♪ La... ♪
: ♪ 啦... ♪
Squidward: ♪ Ahh... ♪
章鱼哥：♪啊……♪
SpongeBob: ♪ Ahh... ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 啊...♪
♪ ...Ahh... ♪
♪ ...啊...♪
♪ Ahh... ♪
♪ 啊...♪
♪ Figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗 ♪
♪ ...Figaro ♪
♪ ...费加罗 ♪
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
:
That's the most wonderful
singing I've ever heard.
：
这才是最美妙的
我听过的歌声。
♪ Ahh... ♪
♪ 啊...♪
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊，是啊，是啊。
Men's Chorus: Here-here,
here-here.
男子合唱：这里这里，
这里-这里。
Bravo, bravo.
太棒了，太棒了。
Yo, Master SquarePants.
哟，方裤大师。
We would be honored
if you would take the open chair
我们将很荣幸
如果你愿意坐在空位上
as our featured soloist.
作为我们的特色独奏家。
Well...
出色地...
Uh, hm...
呃，嗯……
We would also be honored
if you would wear this.
我们也将荣幸
如果你愿意穿这个。
A moustache?
小胡子？
For me?
为我？
Well...
Well, don't be shy.
嗯...
好吧，别害羞。
Put it on.
穿上它。
Squidward, look.
章鱼哥，看。
My very own
choir man's moustache.
我自己的
唱诗班成员的小胡子。
Well, will you do it?
嗯，你会做吗？
Uh, hm...
呃，嗯……
Hm?
嗯？
I'll do it, but only
我会做，但只是
if you find a spot for my
inspiration and great friend...
如果你找到我的位置
灵感和好朋友...
...Squidward.
……章鱼哥。
Deal.
交易。
SpongeBob: ♪ Figaro ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 费加罗 ♪
♪ Figaro ♪
♪ 费加罗 ♪
♪ Figaro. ♪
♪ 费加罗。 ♪